https://www.dotcominfoway.com/privacy-policy/

Dot Com Infoway - Privacy Policy
HomeAbout UsCompany Fact FileMeet the TeamOur ClientsBusiness ModelsMethodologyAlliancesInfrastructureGroup CompaniesAwardsVendor RegistrationTechnologiesMobile SolutionsApp ConsultationMobile Apps DevelopmentMobile App MarketingManaged ServicesDedicated DevelopersWeb SolutionsBusiness ConsultationUI & UX DesignWeb DevelopmentDigital MarketingEducation SolutionsPartner With UsPortfolioBlogResourcesFree SEO ToolCase StudiesWhite PapersEbooksWebinarsContact
GET QUOTE
HomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
Privacy PolicyDCI2018-05-11T12:15:25+05:30 UPDATED ON MAY 11, 2018At Dot Com Infoway, we respect your privacy. According to our privacy policy, we safely handle and protect your information from perversion or misuse. We do not sell or share the information we acquire from you to any third party. We use it only to assist you or help you in enhancing your business.We collect the following information from you:Your name and email address directly from you on visiting our Contact Us page or Live Chat or through the email messages you send us.The details of the web pages visited from the time you enter to the time you leave our website.Comprehensive hits per week for individual web pages for the purpose of statistical records.Usage of InformationWe keep all the business conversations, mail correspondences and documents confidential.We use the information you provide, such as e-mail ID and IM Chat address only to respond to your requests and email you updated on our latest service offerings.When you are logged on to Live Chat assistance, we use the information provided by you to direct you to particular web pages in order to increase the relevance of the information you access through our website.We get the details of the web pages visited by you and the number of page hits per week in order to customize our pages or services and thereby enhance our site’s usability.Third-party service providers used by Dot Com Infoway perform certain functions which may include data processing. Such companies are under a duty of confidentiality of Dot Com Infoway.When required by law, we may disclose your information to law enforcement officials to protect our rights and to comply with the legal proceedings. We reserve the right to notify you of such compliance with the law. GDPR ComplianceAt Dot Com Infoway it has been our long-standing policy to stringently protect the data and privacy of our business partners and our clients. Our internal checks and balances already ensure that when you share your confidential details with us, they are never transferred to a third-party, and all legal and technical measures are taken to make sure that your information is protected and does not fall in wrong hands.Our website and work policy are GDPR-ready. GDPR stands for General Data Protection Regulation and it is a data protection and privacy law applicable to people living in European Union.Complete data protection for our clients is ingrained in our entire work philosophy and Dot Com Infoway has never needed a law to empathize with the concerns of our clients. Nonetheless, we are fully GDPR-compliant with the following data-safety measures:All our data-collection processes and procedures are well-documented and easily accessible to our business partners.We take state-of-the-art security measures to encrypt the data that we store and use.We constantly update our data privacy policies to match them with the best regulations.We never share private information that we get from our clients with third parties and don’t treat such information casually so that it can be misused.Our internal regulations make sure that unauthorized employees don’t have access to sensitive data from our clients.We store our client information on safe environments that are practically impossible to hack.SecurityAt Dot Com Infoway, we follow high-security standards to protect your information. Your valuable data is protected from perversion, loss or any external amendment. Dot Com Infoway strictly restricts access to your information to unauthorized users.Links to other sitesDot Com Infoway’s website contains links to other websites. Our Privacy Policy applies solely to our website. In no way are we responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other sites.E-Mail ListsDot Com Infoway maintains an e-mail Id list of interested clients to inform them about our company, new services, events, the support we offer and much more. This list will not be sold or rented out to any third party. We maintain your details for archival purposes or as otherwise required by law. Users can join our mailing list just by signing up on our website. If you do not wish to continue, you can unsubscribe from our mailing list by following the instructions given on the website.Updates and RevisionAt Dot Com Infoway, we constantly update our website to serve you better. We may also modify our privacy policy without any prior notice. Modifications are with immediate effect once they are posted on the website. On visiting our website you are accepting our Terms and Conditions of using our website.Contact UsIf you have any queries about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us and clarify your doubts.
ABOUT USDot Com Infoway provides 360° Mobile & Web solutions that turn your ideas into world-class products and help you reach your target customer. We have been a leader in creating user-centric and functional business & marketing solutions ever since 2000.OUR PRODUCTSchool Management Software
MOBILE SOLUTIONSiOS App DevelopmentAndroid App DevelopmentMobile Games MarketingIoT Development ServicesWEB SOLUTIONSWeb App DevelopmentBlockchain DevelopmentICO MarketingWallet Integration OTHER LINKSAbout UsCareersPrivacy PolicySitemapConnect With Us Facebook Twitter Pinterest Youtube Instagram LinkedinEmail: ask@dotcominfoway.com
For Job Enquiry Apply Here INDIA3, Vaigai Colony, Ist Floor, Anna Nagar,
Madurai - 625020, Tamilnadu, India.
Phone : +91-452-2522257USA1177 6th Avenue, 5th Floor, New York, NY – 10036 United States. Phone: +1 (646) 513-4044AUSTRALIADot Com Infoway Pty LtdSuite 591, 41/464-480 Kent Street, Sydney, NSW-2000. Phone: +61 2 8071 4317
Copyright © 2000 - 2020 Dot Com Infoway | All Rights Reserved. HomeAbout Us Company Fact FileMeet the TeamOur ClientsBusiness ModelsMethodologyAlliancesInfrastructureGroup CompaniesAwardsVendor RegistrationTechnologiesMobile Solutions App ConsultationMobile Apps DevelopmentMobile App MarketingManaged ServicesDedicated DevelopersWeb Solutions Business ConsultationUI & UX DesignWeb DevelopmentDigital MarketingEducation SolutionsPartner With UsPortfolioBlogResources Free SEO ToolCase StudiesWhite PapersEbooksWebinarsContact
Open chat
1
Powered by Join.chat HelloCan I help you?
